<resources>
    <string name="app_name">ReachUs</string>
    <string name="hint">Enter First Name </string>
    <string name="hint2">Enter Last Name</string>
    <string name="hint3">Enter Phone Number</string>
    <string name="title_activity_login">LoginActivity</string>
    <string name="prompt_email">Email</string>
    <string name="prompt_password">Password</string>
    <string name="action_sign_in">Sign in or register</string>
    <string name="action_sign_in_short">Sign in</string>
    <string name="welcome">"Welcome !"</string>
    <string name="invalid_username">Not a valid username</string>
    <string name="invalid_password">Password must be >5 characters</string>
    <string name="login_failed">"Login failed"</string>
    <string name="aboutus"> Our community ,  ReachUS serves you the safe services. We provide home services such as maid service, repairing, cleaning at your doorstep . We are here for your ease. All the Users here have the flexibility to choose from a variety of services and professionals on this platform.
In case of any inconvenience or doubt , do contact us through contact us section....
</string>
    <string name="about2">Have comfort...... 🙂Relax…..</string>
    <string name="about3">This is our service , your conveniency !!!</string>


    <string name="frg_pass"> Provide your accounts email for which you want to reset your password!</string>
    <string name="termsandconditions">Welcome to the REACHUS club! At ReachUS we are creating a system that strives to reward high trust andcreditworthy individuals of India, inspiring others to be like them. Using the product, you can manageyour cards like a pro, hunt those hidden charges, all the while enjoying rewards from the best brandsin the country.

As REACHUS grows, we aim to help our members discover ways to reduce cost, get superior offerings .It’s about time individuals are celebrated for being good. It’s about time.

Eligibility
By registering with REACHUS and using the App Services, you are representing the following:

You are 18 years of age or older;
You are capable of entering into a legally binding agreement; and
You are not barred or otherwise legally prohibited from accessing or using ReachUS/REACHUS and the App Services.
If you allow anyone to use your account, including individuals under 18 years of age, you will still be responsible for ensuring that such individuals comply with the terms. You will be responsible for all actions these individuals take in and/or through your account. You also acknowledge that ReachUS does not have the responsibility of ensuring that you meet the aforesaid requirements. You agree to comply with all applicable laws when using the Services, and you may only use the Services for lawful purposes.

Please be aware that ReachUS reserves the right to revoke your access to the REACHUS App or App Services, subject to our reasonable discretion. In this regard, we may also choose to suspend your REACHUS Account or your access to the same. As a registered User, in such an event, you may contact our support team to assist you/resolve the situation.

Your Use of ReachUS
When you use our App, you are representing to us that:
a.	Your use of the App shall not violate any applicable law or regulation, and that you fulfil the eligibility criteria set forth under Section 2.
b.	All registration information you submit is truthful, complete and accurate and you agree to maintain accurate, complete and up-to-date account information in your Account.
c.	You are responsible for all activity that occurs under your Account. Unless otherwise permitted by ReachUS in writing, you may only possess one Account.
d.	You are responsible for maintaining the confidentiality of the access credentials of your account and are fully responsible for all activities that occur under your Account. You agree to immediately notify us of any unauthorized use of your passcode or Account or any other breach of security.
e.	Your use of the App, or its content is only for personal purposes. By using the App Services, You hereby agree that the you are aware and responsible for all transactions taking place through your Account. This include the payments made for Credit Cards that are not in the name of the Account Holder, but a family member, friend or acquaintance. By making a payment for a Credit Card that does not belong to You, You assume responsibility for the transactions that have taken place through that Credit Card for the cycle the payment is made by You using the App Services.
f.	Your personal and non-commercial use of the App prevents you from decompiling, reverse engineering, disassembling content, removing any intellectual property right associated with our App, including copyright, trademarks, trade secrets, designs, and patents, or other proprietary notices.
g.	You shall not access or use the App in any manner that may be harmful to the operation of the App or its content.
h.	You shall not use any product or service available on the App for commercial purposes, or use the App Services in any way that is unlawful, or harms ReachUS or any other person or entity.
i.	You will not post, distribute, or otherwise transmit or make available any software or other computer files that contain a virus or other harmful component, or otherwise impair or damage the App or any connected network, or otherwise interfere with any person or entity\'s use or enjoyment of the App.
j.	You will not delete or modify any content of the App, such as legal notices, disclaimers or proprietary notices, copyright or trademark symbols and logos.


Violation of Terms of Use / Suspicious Activity
If we believe that you have violated any of the conditions as mentioned under these Terms or our Privacy Policy, we reserve the right to suspend your access to the App and/or delete your Account without prior notice to You. If we have reason to believe that there is suspicious or unusual activity being carried out through your account, we may temporarily or permanently suspend your access to the App Services. You may reach out to the ReachUS support team to assist you with any query or question arising as a result of the afore-mentioned suspension/ deletion to resolve the same.
You may end your legal agreement with ReachUS at any time by deactivating your account and discontinuing the use of the App Services. We provide all our Users an option through which a User may request archive of a specific Card stored on his/her account or deletion/deactivation of the complete account through the support section on the ReachUS App. Following such request, we consider the agreement to be terminated and take appropriate steps.

Fees
You are responsible for any fees that may be applicable to certain transactions or use of the App; where you will be notified of such applicable fees, prior to the completion of any transaction. Only if you consent to paying the above mentioned fees, shall the transaction go ahead. All fees shall be determined by ReachUS and will be inclusive of taxes.
Refunds
You are responsible for all the information you input in your Account, including the correctness of details for payment of your credit card bill and all charges that result from these payments. ReachUS shall not be responsible for any payment for an incorrect Credit card account or bill payment number. In case, money has been charged to your card or bank account and a payment/service is not delivered by the service provider within 72 working hours of your completion of the transaction then you may inform us regarding the same through the customer support sectionof the ReachUS App. We shall investigate such incidents and if it is found that money was indeed charged to your card or bank account without delivery of the payment/service then you will be refunded the money within twenty one (21) working days from the date of receipt of your email. All refunds will be credited to your card or bank account. ReachUS will have the sole discretion to determine the mode of reversal from the above mentioned options. However, ReachUS disclaims any and all liability, including for refunds, in the event of any error arising from a failure in the applicable bank or credit card service provider’s system or network.
In case a payment has been wrongfully made and credited to your Credit card account or bank account, ReachUS reserve the right to automatically initiate a refund through your bank. By agreeing to these terms, you hereby consent to such a refund initiated by your concerned Bank, at the request of ReachUs, to offset any incorrect transaction, credit or double payment made to your account. Once such transaction is processed, ReachUS shall inform you of the same and the corrective action taken by ReachUS to refund such payment.

Loyalty Points
ReachUS offers its users loyalty points in various forms for their regular and continuous use of the ReachUS App. These loyalty points are provided for performing various actions on the ReachUS App. Each user who makes his/her credit card payments through the ReachUS App earns loyalty points (“ReachUS Coins” or “Coins”). Users are issued Coins at a one to one conversion i.e. every rupee paid towards credit card payments equals to one Coin received by the User. Similarly, each user can also earn loyalty points (“ReachUS Gems” or “Gems”) for referring friends to the Cred App. A user may get rewarded upto 10 (ten) gems for each successful referral. These loyalty points are rewarded purely for the regular use of the ReachUS App and the RachUsApp does not permit any purchase or accrual of these loyalty points in any other way. These loyalty points maybe redeemed by Users to participate in various rewards/offers that are run by the ReachUS App for all users from time to time.
ReachUS reserves the right, at its sole discretion, to change the mode of the accrual of one or any of these types of loyalty points. Further, ReachUS reserves the right to disqualify any User, who does not meet the offer requirements or in case of reasons including but not limited to any misuse of the offer or fraud or suspicious transaction/activity or under any legal requirement or applicable rules and regulations, from receiving any loyalty points. ReachUS also reserved the right to discontinue or change or issue any new form of loyalty points offered at any time, at its sole discretion.

Offers and Rewards
To participate and win rewards and other offers as made available within the App, You must agree to the offer/reward terms and conditions. You agree that your participation in the offer constitutes your understanding of the agreement and to the offer terms and conditions. The offer terms and conditions form a binding legal agreement between you and ReachUS with respect to the offers, and any undefined terms used in the offer terms and conditions shall have the meaning set forth in these terms and conditions. ReachUS reserves the right, at its sole discretion, to disqualify any User who does not meet the offer requirements or in case of reasons including but not limited to any misuse of the offer or fraud or suspicious transaction/activity or under any legal requirement or applicable rules and regulations. ReachUS also reserved the right to discontinue or change any offer or reward or the ReachUS offer programme at any time, at its sole discretion.
For eligibility, in addition to your compliance of these terms and conditions, You must meet the eligibility criteria for each offer to participate. Details of each offer and/or reward and the eligibility terms and conditions for each offer shall be provided in the offers page of your ReachUS App. Offers provided to a particular User may vary from User to User. Please read the offer terms and conditions applicable to your offer as provided in your ReachUS App carefully.

Privacy
We collect, hold, use and transfer your personal data in accordance with our Privacy Policy. By agreeing to the Terms of Use, you hereby agree to our Privacy Policy, which may be updated and/or modified by us from time to time. You understand and agree that, to the extent permitted by applicable law, any data provided by you in connection with the App Services may be shared with our afﬁliates or partners, and/ or used by us for enhancing the App Services, including but not limited to creating new products. Please refer to the Privacy Policy for further clarity on the subject.

 Compliance with NPCI Guidelines
National Payments Corporation of India (‘NPCI’) is an authorized payment system operator by the Reserve Bank of India (‘RBI’).
NPCI owns and operates UPI payment system. A Payment Service Provider (‘PSP’) is the banking company authorized to act as a Payment Service Provider under the UPI framework.
PSP engages the Third Party Application Provider (‘TPAP’) to provide UPI services to You/User.
A TPAP is an entity that provides the UPI compliant app(s) to the end-user customers to facilitate UPI based payment transactions.
The Bank where the end-user customer maintains his/her account and has linked the account for the purpose of debiting/crediting the payment transactions made through UPI is the Customers Bank. The end user customer is the individual who uses UPI payment facility to send and receive payments.
We, ReachUS Technologies Private Limited are a TPAP authorized by NPCI to facilitate payments through Axis Bank. We are a service provider and we participate in UPI through PSP bank.
We are bound by the tripartite agreement entered with the sponsor PSP (Axis Bank) and NPCI. We are responsible for facilitating grievances / complaints resolution of the customers on-boarded on our UPI application.
We shall be the first point of contact for all UPI related grievances/complaints for customers on-boarded by us. In case the complaint/grievance remains unresolved, the next level for escalation will be the PSP Bank, followed by the bank (where you maintain the account) and NPCI in the same order. After exercising these options, you can approach the Banking Ombudsman and/or the Ombudsman for Digital Complaints, as the case may be.

 Disclaimer
The App Services, including all content, software, functions, material, and information made available or accessible through the Services are provided “as is”. ReachUS, ReachUS, their respective agents, co-branders or partners, make no representation and warranty of any kind for the content, software, functions, material, and information available/accessible through the Services.
ReachUS does not warrant that the functions contained in content, information and materials on the App, including, without limitation any third-party sites or services linked to the App will be uninterrupted, timely or error-free, that the defects will be rectified, or that the App or the servers that make such content, information, and materials available are free of viruses or other harmful components.
Further, You understand that a payment transaction is solely between the User who uses the App Services to make his payment (“Sender”) and the User who receives such payment from the Sender (“Recipient”) and that ReachUS does not provide any guarantees or warranties with respect to any User or any service, goods, or delivery level commitment provided by such User. ReachUS cannot assure that other users are or will be complying with the foregoing rules or any other provisions mentioned here. You assume all risk of harm or injury resulting from any such lack of compliance by any other user or any person. You should ensure that you have undertaken adequate due diligence prior to transferring payments using the App Services.

 Limitation of Liability
In no event shall ReachUS, its officers, owners, directors, employees and agents, partners, co-branders, licensors, licensees, consultants, or contractors be liable to you or any third party for any special, incidental, indirect, consequential or punitive damages or losses whatsoever, or damages for loss of data or profits, goodwill, and/ or other intangible loss, whether or not foreseeable and regardless of whether ReachUS has been advised of the possibility of such damages, or based on any theory of liability, including breach of contract or warranty, negligence or other tortious action, or any other claim arising out of or in connection with your use of, or access to, the App or App Services.
In no event shall ReachUS’s total cumulative liability to You in connection with the App Services for all damages, losses and causes of action, arising from or relating to these terms and conditions exceed the net fees ReachUS has actually received and retained from your valid transactions during the three (3) month period immediately preceding the date of the claim.

Governing Law and Jurisdiction
The App, the App Services, all your transactions with the App, and our relationship shall be governed by the laws of India, without regard to conflict of law principles. You agree that all claims, differences and disputes which we may have shall be subject to the exclusive jurisdiction of the competent courts located in Bangalore.
</string>>


    <string-array name="Services">
        <item>Select Main Service</item>
        <item>Car Service</item>
        <item>Repairing Service</item>
        <item>Maid Service</item>
        <item>Cleaning Service</item>
        <item>Home Tutor</item>
        <item>Paste Control</item>
    </string-array>
    <string-array name="carServices">
        <item>Select Secondary Service</item>
        <item>Car Washing</item>
        <item>Car Repairing</item>
    </string-array>
    <string-array name="repairingServices">
        <item>Select Secondary Service</item>
        <item>Plumber</item>
        <item>Electrician</item>
        <item>Carpainter</item>
    </string-array>
    <string-array name="cleaningServices">
        <item>Select Secondary Service</item>
        <item>Home Sanitizing</item>
        <item>Vehicle Sanitizing</item>
    </string-array>
    <string-array name="maidServices">
        <item>Select Secondary Service</item>
        <item>Utensils Cleaning</item>
        <item>Clothes Cleaning</item>
        <item>Home Cleaning</item>
    </string-array>
    <string-array name="bankNames">
        <item>State Bank Of India</item>
        <item>Bank Of Maharashtra</item>
        <item>Punjab National Bank</item>
    </string-array>
</resources>